[
  {
    "questionText": "There are 2 buttons on the screen",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "questionText": "The square root of 81 is 9",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Which book is it, Berenstein Bears or Berenstain Bears? If it's Berenstein put true, and if it's Berenstain put false",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "questionText": "The food item sandwich was named after a person",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "questionText": "The new starwars movies have been worse than the prequals",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "questionText": "You should say Thank you to your mother in english",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Copes law isn't true",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Spiderman dies at the end of the movie infinity war",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "questionText": "This is the 9th question on this quiz",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "questionText": "The derivative of the function y = cot(x) is -csc(x)cot(x) ",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "questionText": "There are no more questions 1",
    "answer": true
  }
]